do you remember a few episodes ago when
we bred a load of cows for leather well
somehow one of them got there
he's just been wandering around i guess
we'll never know
hello everyone and welcome back to
another episode of hermitcraft i have
been very very busy on lots of kind of
boring things to be honest so here is my
base last episode we did some big big
progress and if you look at it closely
you might notice some differences well
on this side it is now snow free well
i've clearly missed some but you can see
how clean it is for the most part on
this side because i wanted to show you
what the difference would be i've left
the snow on
and you can see that these white lines
across it kind of make for for not the
best viewing because when you're moving
around at a distance it kind of creates
this weird optical illusion
so i've been staring at this and i've
decided yep the cleaner version is
definitely the way i'm going so the snow
it's gonna go it's going to have to go
if i was gonna add snow
it would be in a more natural way so i
would like literally add piles up
against the side of the roof in little
amounts
giving it a much nicer more natural
shape than just
blanket sheet of snow but then again i
may not it may just be the odd little
bit where do we go from here
well i said last episode i want to make
some trees and greenery this thing needs
a pop of fresh color something in here
to contrast against this rather cold
looking build but we're going to come
back to the mansion because there's
something more pressing that i want to
do now this is not part of the chest
monster everything you see here is
actually brand new stock for the barge
and that's where we're kicking off
today's episode because it's about time
we did another upgrade oh boy the mumbo
from air campaign is not going well
we are
out of the people that are actually
running
we're the lowest we got the lowest
amount of support what's going on
haven't people been buying diamonds we
totally need to check how many people
have done this two people
two sales here two sales here
and one sale here theoretically that
should be at least a couple of blocks of
support well we won't worry about that
now we'll ask grumbot later what we do
what we do because grumbot you're not
you're not doing your job what we want
to focus on is this
greens well i call it the barge because
it is still technically a barge but it
has upgraded to green's emporium
and i want to sell a little bit of
everything and i've started doing that
but the interior is a little lackluster
it's not very nice in here at all so
we're going to do a big big upgrade
mainly to the inside but we're also
going to build a little bit here
and also a little bit on here just to
give it that extra height you know every
time we get a bit of investment every
time we get lots of sales this thing is
going to grow and grow and grow until i
no longer know what to do with it so
without further ado let's get in
to the build
of the barge 2 electric boogaloo
wait wait wait wait wait hold on hold on
hold on this is not gone to plan at all
oh a wondering trader oh now that's
that's a value that's some valuable
heads right there i'm gonna go get some
emeralds and come back to you later but
here i've had to stop the time lapse
because i've made a mistake quite
look at this look at this mess i started
building and then i sort of looked at it
and i i realized
this is actually a two block center you
know one two three four
but i actually need a
one block center and you can see it's
basically what i'm saying is i done
goofed i need to move the entire thing
all of these
over one block and i must admit
i was getting so frustrated trying to
figure out what was wrong
and i've actually messed around with
this so much i don't know which bits
i've moved and which bits i haven't the
only logical conclusion that i can come
to and it may not be the smartest thing
in the world but i'm gonna blow it up
and start again i'm just gonna take all
of this down
to like this base level here and then
build it back up again the way it should
be i actually believe genuinely believe
that it will be less time
taking it down and starting it over
again than fiddling around trying to
move everything blo a block back and
just repeatedly getting it wrong and
then end up with a mistake somewhere in
the build so i'm just gonna flatten this
and go back again it shouldn't actually
take as long as i think but we're gonna
grab some emeralds for that guy
oh mumbo head
xp head doc head i think we actually
managed to trade every single one
every single one and we got all these
micro blocks that's probably a good
thing to sell at the barge to be honest
i'm still not entirely sure if i want to
go through with this it could be a
mistake and i definitely don't need to
blow up the whole thing but i feel like
i'm gonna be building exactly the same
thing here this is really stupid i gotta
admit this is really stupid but
i
i'm so frustrated with it already that
it's probably for the best to be honest
now this probably won't go well
[Music]
you know what that didn't go too badly
i uh maybe forgot that it's not gonna
drop all the items but that's okay i
have got so much
dark oak and everything that we need for
this build it's absolutely fine this is
what happens when minecraft building
goes wrong you get so frustrated with
the build and you'd rather blow it up
and start again
than just fix the issue
it's so rare to see this
like i never just i never just blow up
my own stuff this feels really strange
i'm usually blowing up other stuff
i think the boomers are going to be out
of a job
oh no
what a mess
this is such a mess
but this is progress
okay i think i've had enough of explodey
time let's get back into the time lapse
and do it properly this time start again
from scratch
get that centerpiece
finished let's go
[Music]
okay i definitely made a mistake that
took longer to completely rebuild it
took me three hours to remake it and you
know what
it looks exactly the same exactly the
same it isn't it is indeed one block
shorter and it is perfect but it looks
identical it looks absolutely identical
however we have added the new addition
of these two parts right here
it goes up these are completely
aesthetic and on the inside we have
totally changed it up it is looking far
more neat and tidy we have two new areas
here and here
and i think we've set the precedent that
we are going to expand upwards from here
this is turning into a really really
zen place to be i've even added like
this garden and i've put the ender chest
the bed and the crafting table here in
the middle which you might need and i've
even included lots of anvils as part of
the design if you ever need to rename
something
now i have to do the really really
boring part of stocking this place up
and that's uh easier said than done
because i've definitely got more barrels
and chests than i do stock
so i'm gonna have to think this through
a little bit the the stock has just been
sitting out here and people have just
been i mean i don't even really need a
shop earlier today mumbo just came in he
just went oh where's the cat where's the
carrots where's the carrots
ah boom boom and he paid dropped a
diamond here
like do i even need a shop forget it
just just leave shulker boxes here in
the open people saw themselves out so
now i'm gonna quickly well relatively
quickly try and put all of these into
the right spots inside the barge
[Music]
wow
all cleared up and installed i have put
in some real effort into making this
one of the best shops in the shopping
district you have your easy access
through the top so you can just fly in
get what you need and zip out again this
is a feature i want to really avoid
losing i really like this and i have
stacked up absolutely everything i
possibly can i mean i don't even know if
we have the time to go through
everything but we got like anvils i can
like quickly whiz through you can stop
on the price if you want to most things
are a diamond per stack it just depends
on how much of a pain they are to get or
craft tnt is quite expensive because you
know tnt and i've also added some like
assorted heads here that i got from the
trader it's all going well this area
needs stocking up and i will probably
get some more stock off camera for this
area i have got the bundle deal a full
box of rockets for eight diamonds
including the shulker box it's going
very very well over here and i've even
because because because i want you to
enjoy your time here at the green
emporium i have added emergency rockets
they are free you just take them if you
get stuck now if people be taking these
rockets when they're not stuck
they're banned from the shop boom i am
chuffed to absolute pieces with this
place i really have become quite
attached to this building and it feels
so pleasant in here now i've mixed two
different styles together i've gone for
a victorian greenhouse meets a japanese
garden and i think i've done a pretty
good job of mixing those two together an
unusual combination
but really quite pleasant well i think
that's enough time at the barge
literally a day
let's head back to the base now i think
we got to take we got to take all this
stuff with us we're basically going to
become the supermarket of the shopping
district we're going to sell a bit of
everything now this is where the item
sorter really comes in handy because i
can just pop in if it's an empty shulker
box i don't need to worry
but anything else
i don't have to sort it
sorting out the endless amount of items
in my base
is just ridiculous and while i was here
i don't know if i did this or if someone
else did this if they did it's probably
the worst prank i've ever seen because
it's two bits of gravel and a redstone
torch my question is why now i'm sure i
didn't do this
is
is that it probably the biggest mystery
of the entire server for me because i'm
pretty sure i didn't do that so now that
we're back at the base there is one
thing i want to do i'm going to get rid
of all the rest of the snow i've decided
that i prefer this it's much much
cleaner and i'm going to figure out
another way
to make the colors pop i have a feeling
it's going to be some flowers and stuff
like that but first i want to get rid of
the snow
won't take long but let's get it done
[Music]
we are officially
snow
free
it feels really good to see it like this
it looks so much cleaner and while i was
there i thought i might as well put
those trees in that i mentioned at the
start of the video and doesn't that look
so much more fresh and clean and
i i really did think that the roses
would pop a little bit more than they do
i think i think the mansion might be a
little bit too big to be popped with
just a couple of uh rose bushes in the
build but overall
i think this looks amazing and i must
admit i always fly around when i'm
showing the mansion like from up here
and you kind of get a really nice
overall view but to really understand
how big this build is we kind of need to
just walk on the floor
and look up and you can get a really
good idea for how imposing this really
is
so the trees have been a huge success i
think they look fantastic
but now
as my t-shirt says
we need to look at what's going on for
the mumbo for mayor campaign
grumbot's got some explaining to do
every episode this mansion gets a little
bit better
a little bit better
i haven't been to see grombot in a while
there he is handsome man right we need a
diamond for you brumbot do something we
are last that's not even a question
anymore it's just it's just do do
something
and by last i mean look at this this is
the visual support meters
lots of support lots of support lots of
support
and there's a mystery supporter there's
there's me there's mumbo there's someone
else who's the mystery supporter either
way
i we're falling behind the more we try
mumbo the less where the less good we do
boop beep
come on granba
do something
my very intelligent robot son
hey hey
he's got a music disc
oh two music discs mumbo for mare and
mumbo for mare
they're not the same disc do i have a
duke i have a g do i have a jukebox
i don't i don't have a jukebox i've got
lots of random items that got mumbo
heads in my ender chest
got mumbo heads but no jukebox do you
reckon that grumbot has a voice has he
has he recorded something for us in his
in his voice
oh b-dubs is there right i've got my
jukebox let's check this out let's see
what let's see what he says
[Music]
he's made a
we're still struggling for air
the heck
there we go we are now flying
and what on earth is that thing what is
that thing
okay
he's made some music on this one is this
music as well
[Music]
it's so annoying
oh my goodness
well if this doesn't win people over i
don't know what will we have to
immediately go and play this to some
people
now stress and iscal already on stresses
campaign
that leaves ren
he's he's all he's also quite close so
why don't we head over to him
and play some of this music without
being seen either subconsciously enter
his mind
okay i can't find ren anywhere
you know what b dubs was in the shopping
district well i don't i think he's
supporting scar but i think he could i
think he could be swayed
let's try it out
maybe maybe this music is exactly what
he needs to hear
of course he might have moved why is he
in the hermit herald
i took damage
there he is
v double o
that's gonna make a little bit of noise
[Music]
he could visibly see him freaking out
and now i mean i wish i looked through
the window here
he he put himself in dirt
let's try the other one and see what he
does
[Music]
we're
do we keep going i feel like we keep
going now we hope that he changes his
allegiance based on those two annoying
songs
i'm starting to question grumbot a
little bit it doesn't seem to have
worked
he's still i want to get close and play
it again
but he's looking he's looking for me
do we play it again
[Music]
i could hear him mining the dirt
well i mean if that annoying music
didn't convince b-dubs to stop
supporting mumbo i don't know what will
oh my goodness
i've just remembered something
i've been wondering
who the mystery supporter is for mumbo
for mayor
it was
scar remember he lost the mining
challenge and he was forced to put his
his support on mumbo's pillar
we haven't got a single legitimate
supporter
not a single one
scars is just a temporary forfeit
mine i'm the campaign manager
and mumbo is mumbo no one likes us
are we not saying mumbo for mayor loud
enough
oh oh there he is oh
hi oh hi there no no no
no
oh look over there at that
hey
no
hold on okay okay okay
[Music]
and we're out
i mean he could have just pressed tab
and seen that i was the only person
online and also it's only gonna be me or
mumbo isn't it
okay i'm back at the base and i've been
thinking about what i want to do next to
the base and i don't think this project
may ever be finished but i spoke about
this before i want to go down from here
now that is gonna take some proper
designing so i'm not gonna start that
for at least a couple of episodes but
it's the next logical thing what i did
notice is is that rendog is currently
online which means he might be back at
the hangar
sneaky sneaky
there he is
now we just need to get close enough so
that he can hear the music
why has he got a why has he got a poster
here
scar
see seriously scar
why have you put a poster underground or
maybe it was here and then he just
he just terrained over the top this is
probably like a screenshot for the worst
campaign placement
but actually while we're here
underground if we could just find his
username
we could play it from under here and he
probably won't find us
he keeps getting oh oh he probably can
hear me digging around okay let's just
try it
does the name tag
[Music]
what on earth are they gonna say like
what
just i can't imagine their reactions if
i heard this song out of the blue i'd be
like what in queen elizabeth's shiny
crown
was that
let's try let's try the other one
let's try to get it
[Music]
i think we've successfully got another
supporter
and now we leave oh i've been seen
[Music]
bail
fail
we've been we've been rumbled
well i think that is enough for today's
episode i had an amazing time today now
i know i didn't upload for a week and
that's because i also have lots to do
in my life other than make videos so
occasionally it takes a little longer it
doesn't mean that i'm working on the
video for a whole week it just means
that i'm busy that is all
now i do want to share some amazing
pictures with you these are from a
reddit user called similarity city
and they have made some what is that
that is a parrot on top of mumbo's base
that is weird
they are an artist from reddit that i
found and their art of grumba is so good
i genuinely want to make my own poster
out of it so take a look at these from
similarity city they are absolutely
gorgeous this fan art is some of my
favorite that i've ever seen and i just
wanted to i just wanted to give them a
proper shout out on the channel because
this is absolutely amazing and it
probably took a very very long time but
anyway that is enough for today's
episode we have played some music we
upgraded the barge and we've done some
base work today
tidying up the snow which apparently
i've missed a lot of
i don't think it matters if it's on the
back to be honest
oh there's quite a lot
let's just not look at it all right i
shall see you in the next episode good
bye
you